<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Golang on Bruno Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/golang/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Golang on Bruno Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/golang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spying on my dog without a SD Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024-06-30-spying-on-my-dog-without-sd-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024-06-30-spying-on-my-dog-without-sd-card/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently, I bought a camera to record Alex (my dog) when he is alone at home. However, after some initial research, I found that this camera only allows recording with an SD card. Additionally, when the SD card is being used for recording, I can&amp;rsquo;t use the RTSP (Real-Time Streaming Protocol).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since I don&amp;rsquo;t want to buy multiple SD cards for the several cameras I plan to have in the future, the best solution would be to have a program that records and saves the footage to a specific location, such as an HDD, without needing an SD card.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyGo in Microcontrollers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-05-26-tinygo-in-microcontrollers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-05-26-tinygo-in-microcontrollers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently (at work) I had to flash a microcontroller to simulate a keyboard. The problem was that I didn&amp;rsquo;t knew anything about microcontrollers (still don&amp;rsquo;t) or even how could I flash those.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the time I was using the &lt;a href=&#34;http://digistump.com/products/1&#34;&gt;Digispark&lt;/a&gt; microcontroller since it was cheap and it was user friendly (with an external case, the device looks like a normal usb). Then a co-worker helped me on the flashing process and for that we used &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.arduino.cc/en/software&#34;&gt;Arduino IDE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
