<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Red Teaming on Bruno Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/red-teaming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Red Teaming on Bruno Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/red-teaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Frontend Lies Backend Spies - C2 Redirector</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-08-05-frontend-lies-backend-spies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-08-05-frontend-lies-backend-spies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we’ll walk through a possible architecture for setting up a C2 redirector using Nginx to front and forward traffic to a Mythic C2 server. The goal is to create a stealthy, realistic-looking infrastructure that blends in with normal web traffic — making it harder for defenders to detect or block command-and-control activity. We’ll cover the use of decoy subdomains, SSL certificates, traffic redirection, and how to configure everything to work seamlessly together.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Teaming EP2 and 3: C2 and Smishing Simulation &#43; C2 and Usb Implant</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-07-18-redteaming-ep2e3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-07-18-redteaming-ep2e3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are the final pieces on red team engagements that I wrote during my time at ArtResilia. Here, we cover smishing simulations and USB implants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.artresilia.com/red-teaming-ep2-c2-and-smishing-simulation/&#34;&gt;Second article&lt;/a&gt; - In this article, we talk about C2 and Smishing Simulation — the focus is on the execution of a smishing campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.artresilia.com/red-teaming-ep3-c2-and-usb-implant/&#34;&gt;Third article&lt;/a&gt; - In this article, we talk about C2 and USB Implant — the focus is on deploying and using a USB implant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hash Cracking in The Cloud</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-06-12-hash-cracking-in-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-06-12-hash-cracking-in-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cracking passwords at scale requires serious GPU power — and serious money. I quickly realized that building a dedicated machine with multiple GPUs wasn&amp;rsquo;t just expensive upfront (thanks to hardware and GPU prices), but also a constant drain due to electricity costs. Worst of all, the rig would sit idle most of the time, wasting its potential. So I started looking for a smarter, more flexible setup. That led me to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hashtopolis&#34;&gt;Hashtopolis&lt;/a&gt;, a powerful tool for distributed hash cracking; &lt;a href=&#34;https://vast.ai/&#34;&gt;Vast.ai&lt;/a&gt;, a platform offering affordable on-demand GPU instances; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-one/connections/connect-networks/&#34;&gt;Cloudflare Tunnel&lt;/a&gt;, which lets me expose my Hashtopolis server securely to the internet — no public IP or port forwarding needed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Teaming EP1: C2 and Phishing Simulation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-11-06-redteaming-ep1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023-11-06-redteaming-ep1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the first of three articles that will be published concerning social engineering campaigns during red teaming exercises (while I was working at ArtResilia).&#xA;Follow this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.artresilia.com/red-teaming-ep1-c2-and-phishing-simulation/&#34;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt; for the original blog post.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
